（愛花・回想）真広→
Mahiro...
それは
こう尋ねているのですね？→
So, what you're asking...
「お前は
俺の女になれるのか？」と
is if I would be your woman?
（不破真広）いや　そこまで
品のねぇこと言ってねぇよ
No, I wouldn't be that crass.
（愛花）ふっ…　では　妹と一体→
Well, then...
Exactly how do you want to end up with your little sister?
どうなりたいというんです？
何が妹だ。　お前
俺を兄なんて思ってないだろ
Little sister, my ass.
You don't think of me as an older brother.
（愛花）当たり前です
血もつながってませんし
Of course not.
We're not even related by blood.
なあ　なんで　お前なんだ
Why does it have to be you?
不合理だろ
This doesn't make any sense.
今までつきあった女と真逆で→
You're the exact opposite of the girls I date.
色気も胸も全然ないのに
どうして　こう気になるんだ
You have no boobs or sexiness...
Why do you interest me?
やたら落ち着かないんだ
Why can't I keep my cool?
You aren't getting enough sleep.
（愛花）睡眠不足ですよ
そんなわけあるか！
That's not it!
愛花　とにかく→
Aika...
For the time being, don't start a relationship with anyone.
しばらく
誰とも　どうともなるな
俺に逆らうな。　いいな？
Don't disobey me, got it?
（愛花）では　すでに誰かと
どうにかなっていた場合は→
In that case,
what would you do if I were already in a relationship?
どうします？
はっ…
D-Don't tell me you have a boyfriend!
まっ　まさか　彼氏がいんのか!?
（愛花）
合理的に考えて　どうでしょう？
Considering it rationally, what do you think?
「愛が運命を導くか→
Whether love leads fortune,
それとも運命が愛を導くか」…。
or else fortune love.
For 'tis
（滝川吉野）
「それは　われらの人生が→
a question left us yet to prove.
めいめい試さねばならぬ問題だ」。
Episode 7
First Kiss
何やってんだ？
防寒だよ→
What are you doing?
Protecting us from the cold.
冷たい風が入ってこないように。
葉風さんは？
I'm keeping the cold air out.
Where's Ms. Hakaze?
She said something about gathering her strength before the final battle.
決戦の前に　英気を養うやら
なんやら言ってたからな。
ふっ…　どうせ→
I'm sure she's just drooling in her sleep.
よだれでも垂らして
眠りこけてるんだろ。
あっ　ほら。
Oh, here.
これ　どうしたんだ？
Where'd you get this?
I borrowed it from the house where we slept.
泊まらせてもらった家から
借りてきたんだ。
You're really something.
すげぇな　お前。　ちゃっかり泥棒。
A shameless thief.
借りただけだよ！
ちゃんと返すから→
I just borrowed it!
I'm going to return it!
After it's all over.
全部終わったら…。
全部終わったら？
After it's all...
over.
（心の声）
≪結果は　どうなるとしても→
Regardless of the outcome,
もうすぐ
すべての不合理が正される≫
all the irrationalities will soon be redressed.
≪愛花ちゃんを殺した犯人が
見つかったら→
Once Aika's killer is found,
真広は　迷うことなく
その手にかけるだろう≫
I have no doubt that Mahiro will kill him.
≪復讐…≫
Revenge...
That's the only reason for the current Mahiro's existence.
≪そのためだけに
今の真広は存在するんだから≫
≪だとしたら
復讐が終わった　その先は？≫
Given that,
what will happen once he's gotten his revenge?
Received Messages
It's been a while.
久しぶりだな。
えっ？
お前　しょっちゅう
携帯　じ～っと眺めてたけど→
You always used to stare at your phone.
それ　しなくなったろ　最近。
But you've stopped recently, right?
うぅ…　腹立つくらい寒いな。
It's so damn cold...
≪あの日…≫
That day...
That day was hot.
≪あの日は　暑くて…≫
愛花ちゃん
こんなに　宿題残してたの？
Aika, you still have all this homework left to do?
It's irrational to give us so much homework that we can't enjoy our summer vacation.
（愛花）夏休みに
人を休ませることのない宿題が→
出るなんて　不合理ですから
もう…
キス
えっ？
Kiss.
夏が終わる前にしましょうか
Will we kiss before summer ends?
Huh? Well...
えっ!?　それは…　あっ！
あっ…
ここでは嫌ですよ
Not here, though.
I'd have to agree with that.
僕も　それは同意見だけど…
Since it's our first time,
初めて同士なんだし
場所にも　こだわりたいですね
we should choose the location with care.
吉野さんに
考えはありますか？
Do you have any ideas, Yoshino?
ええ～？
いきなり言われても…
I can't think of one right now...
Do you have an idea, Aika?
じゃあ
愛花ちゃんには考えあるの？
とびきりの場所があるんです
I have the perfect place.
別荘？
（愛花）ええ。→
A summer house?
Yes.
夏休みの最後の１週間は
毎年　家族で過ごすんです
We always spend the last week of summer vacation there as a family.
You're inviting me, too?
そこに僕も？
両親も　きっと喜びます
I'm sure my parents would be happy to have you.
でも　真広と１週間も一緒か…
But a week with Mahiro?
You'd be with me, as well...
（愛花）私とも一緒なんですよ？
う～ん…
（愛花）吉野さん　真広と
仲よくしてあげてください。→
Yoshino, please be friendly to Mahiro.
あの人の友達になれるのは
吉野さんぐらいなんですから
I'm pretty sure that you're about the only one who could be his friend.
≪愛花ちゃん…≫
Aika...
≪真広の気持ち
気付いてるんだろ？≫
You know how Mahiro feels, don't you?
≪だったら…≫
Then...
Fuwa Mahiro
ピッ
真広
Mahiro?
You're free, right?
暇だろ　今から駅前に来いよ
Meet me at the station.
いきなり　暇って
断定しないでほしいんだけどな…
I'd prefer that you not just assume that I'm free...
じゃ　１０分後な
１０分!?　早すぎだって！
Okay, see you in ten minutes.
Ten minutes?
That's not enough time.
ツーツー（不通音）
おい！
Hey!
まったく…
Jeez...
（２人）ふふっ　こんにちは～！
Hello!
なっ！　おい　真広…
Hey, Mahiro...
Let me introduce you.
紹介するよ。　こいつ　滝川吉野
This is Takigawa Yoshino.
Yoshino?
（女子大生）
吉野君？　珍しい名前
What a unique name.
Hey, wait...
ちょっと待って
僕　やっぱり用が…
On second thought, I'm busy...
うわっ！
さっ　行こうぜ
Come on, let's go.
He's so cute!
かわいい～
やばい　年下いいかも！
His being younger might not be so bad.
But you always go for someone older than you.
真広　これは　ちょっと
許されないんじゃないか？
Mahiro, I don't think I can forgive this.
That's that, and this is this.
許されなかったらどうなるんだ？
So what if you don't?
Judgment.
成敗！
（女子大生たち）すご～い！
Wow!
（女子大生）超イケてる！
（女子大生）ねえ～
So cool.
I know.
（２人）わあ！
あっ
（女子大生）きゃあ！
（女子大生）やだ　二人ともうまい
Wow, they're both so good...
They're like pros.
もうプロじゃん
ふふっ
Right?
ねえ？
（２人）ん？
ちょっと…
なんなの？
Hey...
What's this?
（２人）もう…
バイバ～イ
Bye!
おい
ん？
Hey...
ああいうの　本当にやめてくれ
迷惑なんだ
You should seriously cut that out.
It's inconvenient.
What the hell?
なんだよ　人が　せっかく
彼女つくってやろうってのに
And here I was, trying to get you a girlfriend.
Who asked you to?
そんなの　誰が頼んだ
随分と余裕があるのな
You seem pretty confident.
お前の性格じゃあ
ほっといたら　いつまでも…
I didn't think you could get one alone, given your personality...
彼女って
欲しいからつくるとか→
A girlfriend
isn't something you get
just because you want one.
そういうものじゃないだろ
ん？
You meet someone you like,
好きな子ができて
その子と一緒にいたいから…→
and you want to spend time together.
だから→
That's why
you'd want her as your girlfriend, right?
彼女になってほしいって
思うんだろ　そういうのは
What?
なんだよ？
しらけた
はあ？
I just lost interest.
Huh?
夏休みとはいえ
こんな時間に帰宅とは→
Even if it's summer vacation,
you have some nerve, coming home this late.
いいご身分ですね
吉野につきあってやってたんだ
吉野さん？
I was keeping Yoshino company.
Yoshino?
I thought he might want a girlfriend or two,
あいつだって　いいかげん
彼女の一人も欲しいだろうから→
so I thought I'd introduce him to some girls.
女を紹介してやろうと思ってな
He didn't seem too dissatisfied.
吉野だって
まんざらでもなさそうだったし
真広なんかの知り合いに→
I find it hard to believe
that you hang out with anyone who'd suit Yoshino.
吉野さんとつきあえる人が
いるとは思えませんけど
I wouldn't say that...
そうでもないぞ
いいとこの女子大生とかいてな
There were some rich college girls.
「君の鎖骨を
箸でつまんでみたいなぁ」→
There's no way a rich college girl would be able to stand
とか言いそうな
ゆがんだ吉野さんに→
that twisted Yoshino who'd say something like,
いいとこの女子大生が
耐えられるわけありませんよ
"I'd like to pick at your clavicle with chopsticks."
お前の吉野像が
悪意で　ゆがんでるよ
Your image of Yoshino seems a bit spiteful.
いいですか？　吉野さんは→
Simply put,
If you want to be positive about it, Yoshino has a high degree of adaptability.
よく言えば順応性が高く
悪く言えば主体性がないんです。→
But if you want to be negative about it, he has no individuality.
どんな　むちゃくちゃな状況でも→
He can act normally under any circumstance,
普通に
行動することができますが→
but he will not take personal initiative
自分で　積極的に動いたり
状況を変えようとすることはない
or try to change the status quo.
Therefore, it is not in his character to take the lead with women.
だから　およそ
女性を引っ張っていくような→
気質ではありません
ふ～ん
逆に　引っ張ってもらわないと
ダメなタイプです
He's the opposite, one who needs another to lead him.
普通の女性なら
あんな　煮えきらない人は→
Any normal woman
would dismiss someone who can't speak for himself.
願い下げでしょう
まあ　それは　もっともだけどよ
Well, I guess that's true.
吉野さんと合うのは→
The one best suited for Yoshino
真広みたいなのです
うっ！　俺？
would be someone like you, Mahiro.
Me?
気ままで身勝手で　なんでも
自分の思いどおりにしたがって→
You're carefree and selfish,
and do whatever you please.
人を振り回しても　まったく
気にしない　王族みたいな人。→
You don't care how much you manipulate others,
somewhat like royalty.
そういう人にとって
吉野さんは最適でしょう
I'm sure Yoshino would be ideal for someone like that.
Give me a break with that kind of stuff.
気持ち悪いこと言うなって
別に　男同士でつきあえなんて
言ってるわけじゃありませんよ
I didn't say that you two should start dating.
I'm simply stating that there aren't many women
真広のような
横暴で尊大な女性など→
as tyrannical and pompous as you.
そうはいないと言ってるんです
それでも　真広は
吉野さんを大切にした方がいい
Even so,
I think you should treat Yoshino well.
What?
あの人は　何があっても→
I'm certain that no matter what happens,
必ず
味方になってくれるでしょうから
he will stay by your side.
はぁ…
真広には　ほんと参るよな
Mahiro seriously wears me out...
I wonder if he really knows about Aika and me.
もしかして
僕と愛花ちゃんのこと→
感づいてたりするんだろうか
Maybe that's why he was trying so set me up...
だから　無理やり　彼女なんて…
いや　それはないか
No, that can't be it.
あいつ　勘は働くくせに
肝心なところは鈍いし
He's really perceptive, but utterly oblivious when it matters.
愛花ちゃん！
Aika!
はぁ…　あの兄妹には→
Those siblings really are something...
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
ほんと　振り回されるよ
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
Girlfriend
How was the college girl's
clavicle?
・ブオォーー！
ああ～　うっせぇ　寝られやしねぇ。
Damn, it's loud...
I can't sleep at all.
意外とデリケートなんだ。
I had no idea you were so delicate.
Why not?
意外でもなんでもねぇよ
俺は　お坊ちゃんだからな。
I'm a sheltered rich boy, you know.
自分で言うか。
So you admit it.
なあ。
ん？
Hey.
お前　昔　言ってたろ→
Didn't you say before
ほれた女とつきあえなきゃ
彼女なんていたって意味ねぇって。
that there's no point in having a girlfriend
if it isn't someone you actually like?
そんなこと言ったっけ？
Did I?
それ　よく分からねぇ。
I don't really get that.
いつも向こうから言い寄られて…。
They were the ones to ask me out.
It's always been that way...
そんなんばっかだったからさ。
なあ
好きな女とつきあう気分って→
So, what's it like?
どんな感じなんだ？
Dating someone you like?
どうなんだろうな。
I wonder that myself...
どんな形であれ
別れって　必ず来るだろ。
No matter what kind,
some form of separation always occurs, right?
I think that might be harder to accept
好きな人とつきあえたら→
余計に　それを考えるの
きついんじゃないか？
if you're dating someone you really like.
そんなもんか。
そんなもんだよ。
You think so?
Yeah, I do.
星　きれいだな。
The stars are pretty, aren't they?
前も　星　見たよな　一緒に。
We've looked at stars together before, haven't we?
ああ…　俺ん家の別荘でか。
Yeah...
At the family summer house?
Yeah, summer vacation.
うん　夏休み。
あれ？　お前　星　嫌いだって
言ってなかったっけ？
Wait.
Didn't you say you hated stars?
冬の星は好きなんだよ。
I like the stars in winter.
なんつうか
々しくて　冷たいっていうか。
I can't explain it well, but they're sort of dignified and cold.
ちょっとやそっとじゃ届かない
高～い所にあって…。
They're up high, and can't easily be reached.
Mahiro might never realize
≪真広は
一生　気付かないかもしれない→
that he was in love with Aika.
自分が　愛花ちゃんに
ただ恋をしていたってことを≫
≪あの真広が　愛花ちゃんには→
Despite his personality,
Mahiro was afraid to even touch Aika.
触れるのさえ緊張していた≫
≪そばにいても
どうしていいか戸惑っていた≫
He never knew what to do when he stood next to her.
≪愛花ちゃんも
口では　なんと言っていても→
Regardless of what she may have said,
I'm pretty sure Aika didn't hate Mahiro.
真広を嫌ってはいなかったろう≫
≪出会い方が違えば
あるいは　二人は…≫
If they'd met under different circumstances,
those two might well have...
待て　真広！　愛花ちゃん！
Wait, Mahiro...
Aika!
邪魔！　ああ～　めんどくせぇ
Out of the way.
How annoying...
"Do whatever is possible with your own hands."
（愛花）
できることは　自分たちの手で。→
それが　お父様の方針でしょ
Is that not Father's policy?
It's a shame your parents suddenly couldn't come.
でも　ご両親が
来られなくなっちゃうなんて…
お仕事ですから
しかたありません
They had work, so there was no other way.
あっ　吉野さん　手が空いたら
階段も拭いておいてください
Oh, Yoshino...
When you're done, could you mop the stairs?
はぁ…　はい
Sure.
お前　吉野のこと
ほんっと　嫌いなんだな
You really hate Yoshino, don't you?
What?
えっ？
別荘に誘うなんて→
You just invited him here
to vent out your frustrations by working him to the bone, right?
思い切り　こき使って
憂さ晴らししようっていうんだろ
それとも
なんか企んでるのか？
Or were you plotting something else?
企み…
ふふっ　そうかもしれませんね
Plotting?
You may be right.
ジューー（肉を焼く音）
ああっ　お前！
Hey!
そんな　いっぺんに焼いたら
焦げるだろ！
If you grill that much, it'll burn!
And you should have put on the sauce before cooking!
真広こそ　そのソースは　お肉を
焼く前に塗っておくべきでしょう！
まあ　まあ　楽しく食べようよ
Now, now...
Let's all try to enjoy the food...
はぁ…
僕が焼かせていただきます
I'll take over the grill.
あっ　次　もろこしな　吉野
僕も食べたいんだけど…
I want some corn next, Yoshino.
I'd also like to eat, you know.
Girlfriend
After dinner, let's meet
in the backyard.
おい　焦げてるぞ　吉野
あっ…　ははっ
Hey!
It's burning, Yoshino.
うわぁ～
Wow...
すごい
（愛花）でしょう？
Amazing.
Isn't it?
私たちの暮らす街では→
We can't see all these stars in the city.
ここまでの星は
見ることができない
I've never seen so many stars...
こんなに　いっぱいの星
見たことないよ
It's almost like they'll spill out of the sky.
こぼれ落ちそうなぐらい
（愛花）夏の星は
本当に節操がないですからね→
Summer stars are so unscrupulous.
めったやたらと輝いて
They shine without thought or care.
愛花ちゃん　星　嫌いなの？
Do you not like the stars, Aika?
I like them.
好きです
えっ？
Huh?
They try so hard to display their radiance.
輝きを
必死に誇示しようとする
Trying to let us know they exist before they disappear.
消えゆく間際に
自分が　ここにいるということを→
分かってもらおうと
I admire that simple, honest wish.
その愚直な願いが好きです
Aika...
愛花ちゃん…
吉野さんは　ここにいますね
Yoshino, you're here, right?
Yes.
愛花ちゃんも…
And you, too.
・吉野　どこだ？
Where are you, Yoshino?
What're you two doing?
あっ　何やってんだよ　お前ら
Let's play some cards.
おい　トランプしようぜ
別荘っていったら
まずは　これだろ
You have to play cards at a summer house.
ふぅ…　では
負けた人が朝食の準備ですね
Well, then the loser's making breakfast.
What?
げっ！　お前も交ざんのかよ
（愛花）当たり前です
You're playing, too?!
Of course.
っていうか
お前ら　何やってたんだ？
What were you doing out here, anyway?
あっ…　えっと　星　見てたんだ
Um, we were looking at the stars...
ああ～　夏の星って苦手だ
I don't like the summer stars.
They shine without a care in the world.
無節操に光りまくって
なんか　かゆくなってくる
They make me uncomfortable.
部屋　戻ろうぜ
Let's go back to the house.
（愛花）携帯→
Please set your phone on vibrate.
マナーモードに
しておいてくださいね
Huh?
ああ～　むかつく！
Goddamit!
お前
トランプ　やたら強いこと→
Why the hell didn't you tell me you were so good at cards?
なんで　今まで隠してたんだよ
そんなプロフィール
わざわざ言うことじゃないだろ
It isn't exactly something you tell people.
愛花も強いんだよな
俺より　頭悪いくせにさ
Aika's pretty tough, too...
Ringer on Vibrate
Even though she's not as smart as I am.
吉野
ん？
Yoshino.
愛花と　二人きりに
ならない方がいいぜ
It's better that you aren't caught alone with Aika.
えっ？
愛花のヤツ→
She plots evil things.
邪悪なこと
考えてるっぽいからさ
邪悪な？
Evil what?
出会ったころから
そうだったんだよな
She's always been like that.
あいつの考えは分からねぇ
I can never figure out what she's thinking.
つっけんどんで
かわいげなくて→
She's always blunt and never cute.
こんな女と一緒に暮らすなんて
無理だって思った
I thought she'd be impossible to live with.
なのに　いつの間にか　するっと→
But before I knew it,
家族の中に溶け込んでた
she'd become a part of the family.
As if she'd always belonged here.
するっと　入ってくんだよな
ほんと　何考えてんだか…
Seriously, what the hell is she thinking?
愛花ちゃんが　何考えてるか→
Do you really want to know
真広は知りたいのか？
what she's thinking?
Yeah.
ああ　しゃくだからな
It's irritating.
あのさ…
ん？
You know...
お前　愛花ちゃんを…
The way you feel about Aika...
ん？
いや…
Nothing.
この分だと　１週間ずっと
お前が朝食当番だな
At this rate, you'll be in charge of breakfast all week.
（愛花）野生の勘
働くんでしょうか？　真広は
I wonder
if Mahiro's instincts are alerting him.
う～ん…
（愛花）このままじゃ　いつまでも→
At this rate, I don't think we'll ever be able to do it.
できそうにありませんね
あっ…
吉野さんが
男らしく引っ張ってくれないから
Because you won't lead like a man.
I'm not sure how to respond...
そんなこと言われても…　あっ！
Aika, that's dangerous!
愛花ちゃん　危ないって！
あ…　愛花ちゃん？
Aika...
吉野さん…
Yoshino.
やっぱり　やめておきます
Never mind.
えっ？　愛花ちゃん…
Aika?
（愛花）
ひまわりに見られていますから
The sunflowers are watching.
愛花…　ちゃん…
Aika...
うっ…　寒っ。
It's cold.
はぁ…。
起きたか。
You're awake?
いよいよだな　吉野。
それ…。
It's finally time, Yoshino.
That's...
魔具なんざ
興味ないと思ってたけど…。
I didn't think I'd be interested in talismans, but...
さすがに盛り上がる。
I gotta say, I'm pretty excited.
はははっ
何　本気で　びびってんだよ。
Why do you look so scared?
撃つわけないだろ。
I'm not gonna shoot you.
「決心は記憶の奴隷にすぎぬ→
Purpose is but the slave to memory.
記憶次第でどうとでもなる」。
What we do determine, oft we break.
「ハムレット」か…　悪くないな。
Hamlet, huh?
Not bad.
今日で　この復讐劇も終わりだ。
Today marks the end of this revenge play.
But look,
≪「見たまえ　夜明けの空が
茜色の衣をまとって→
the morn, in russet mantle clad,
あの東の丘の露を踏みつつ
越えて来る」≫
walks o'er the dew of yon high eastward hill.
Let's go.
行くぞ。
ああ。
Yeah.
kimi to miteta nagareboshi oikakete
Chasing the shooting star that we saw together
Reaching this place all alone
hitori bocchi konna toko made kiteta
Hiding the feelings I wanted to express to you
kinou kimi ni ienakatta kimochi o
kotoba no naka kakusu no
within words
tooku hanarete itemo douka todokimasu you ni
No matter how far we are separated,
please let it reach you
kono michi no saki ni matsu unmei nante
The fate waiting for us down this road
is not yet known
ima wa mada
dare mo mada
shiranai kedo
by anyone
To the future drawn by numbed fingers
kajikan da yubisaki de egaita mirai he
With you we can make it
kimi to nara ikerutte
nee sonna ki ga shiteta nda
That's what I feel
kitto
with certainty
今日で　何かが変わると思うか？
Do you think anything will change starting today?
（葉風）
雌雄を決するときが来たな　左門。
Time to see how this fight ends, Samon.
（左門）ならば　姫様
今日で　その運　尽きさせましょう。
Very well, Princess.
Today, let us put an end to your good fortune.
（潤一郎）そのため
この世界は　一度　消滅する。
To do so, the world will first be destroyed.
（山本）出たわね　絶園の樹。
There you are, Tree of Exodus.
「ただ…
ただ復讐さえすればいいのだ」。
Revenge...
Revenge is all that matters.
Episode 8
The Hour to Suppress
the Princess